Guide to the Arthur and Luce Klein Spoken Arts Records
Yale University Music Library
- Artist contracts, Series IV
  - SAC812, SAC7115, SAC7116, SAC8015: Romeo and Juliet, Henry IV and Henry V, 1961 (Box 35, Folder 567)
  - SAC814: Poems - Blake and Hopkins, 1961 (Box 35, Folder 568)
  - SAC818: Love Poems by Lawrence Durrell - Curtis Brown, 1961–1998 (Box 36, Folder 569)
  - SAC820: Golden Treasury of Chidren's Verse, 1961–1993 (Box 36, Folder 570)
  - SAC822: French Literature, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 571)
  - SAC823 and SAC824: Just so Stories - Jill Balcon, 1961–1993 (Box 36, Folder 572)
  - SAC829 and SAC49-3: Spanish Verse, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 573)
  - SAC830 and SAC978: The Pit and the Pendulum and Tell-Tale Heart, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 574)
  - SAC831 and SAC49-5: Spanish Prose, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 575)
  - SAC832: Walden - Henry David Thoreau, 1962–1998 (Box 36, Folder 576)
  - SAC834: Books and the Bad Life, 1962–1993 (Box 36, Folder 577)
  - SAC838 and SA47-1: French Songs for Children, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 578)
  - SAC839 and SAC50:3 Latin American Poetry - Spanish American Verse, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 579)
  - SAC840: Grimm's Fairy Tales I, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 580)
  - SAC841 and SAC47-4: Scenes de la vie Fran, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 581)
    French. Non-royalty contract.
  - SAC842: Emerson - Poems and Essays, 1962, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 582)
  - SAC845 and SAC846: Grimm's Fairy Tales II, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 583)
  - SAC847: Fairy Tales - Perrault, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 584)
  - SAC848: Illiad and Odyssey - Prof. Ennis Rees, 1962, 1968-1998 (Box 36, Folder 585)
  - SAC849 and SAC983: Illiad and Odyssey - Prof. Ennis Rees, 1967–1998 (Box 36, Folder 586)
  - SAC850: Moby Dick, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 587)
  - SAC852: and SAC49-2: Spanish Dictations I, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 588)
  - SAC853: and SAC50-2: Spanish Dictations II, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 589)
  - SAC856: Gulliver's Travels, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 590)
  - SAC857: Nursery Rhymes, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 591)
  - SAC858: Treasury of Tennyson, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 592)
  - SAC858 and SAC8017: Treasury of Donne, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 593)
  - SAC860 and SAC8023: Treasury of Wordsworth, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 594)
  - SAC861 and SAC8029: Treasury of Browning, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 595)
  - SAC862, SAC863, SAC864, SAC50-6, SAC86-3, and SAC86-4: Treasury of Spanish Drama I, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 596)
  - SAC865 and SAC49-1: Spanish Songs for Children, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 597)
  - SAC866 and SAC7120: Treasury of Dryden, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 598)
  - SAC867 and SAC8018: Treasury of Milton, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 599)
  - SAC868 and SAC8027: Treasury of Keats, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 600)
  - SAC869 and SAC8026: Treasury of Shelley, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 601)
  - SAC870: A Man is a Man, 1963–1998 (Box 36, Folder 602)
  - SAC871: Hans Christian Anderson I, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 603)
  - SAC872: Hans Christian Anderson II, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 604)
  - SAC873, SAC874, SAC875, SAC876, and SAC877: Hans Christian Anderson III, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 605)
  - SAC878: Rabelais, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 606)
  - SAC879 and SAC47-3: Dictees Elementaires, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 607)
  - SAC880 and SAC7010: As You Like It, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 608)
  - SAC881: Henry VIII, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 609)
  - SAC882 and SAC8013: Midsummer Night's Dream, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 610)
  - SAC883: Much Ado About Nothing, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 611)
  - SAC884 and SAC7111: Taming of the Shrew, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 612)
  - SAC885: Treasury of Nursery Rhymes II, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 613)
  - SAC886 and SAC8014: The Tempest, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 614)
  - SAC887 and SAC7112: Twelfth Night, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 615)
  - SAC888 and SAC7113: Comedy of Errors, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 616)
  - SAC889: Cymbeline, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 617)
  - SAC890: Richard II, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 618)
  - SAC891 and SAC7117: Richard III, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 619)
  - SAC892: Troilus and Cressida, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 620)
  - SAC893 and SAC7114: The Two Gentlemen of Verona, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 621)
  - SAC894: A Winter's Tale, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 622)
  - SAC895, SAC 909, SAC57-5, and SAC 57-6: Fables de la Fontaine - G. Riquier, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 623)
  - SAC896 and SAC8005: Elizabethan Love Poems, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 624)
  - SAC897: Treasury of Lewis Carroll, 1964 (Box 37, Folder 625)
  - SAC898: Longfellow - Donald Hall, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 626)
  - SAC899: Irish Revol.utionary Songs, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 627)
  - SAC901: Love in Shakespeare, 1964-1975, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 628)
    Royalty statement included. Non-royalty contract.
  - SAC903: Wisdom for our Day, 1964–1992 (Box 37, Folder 629)
  - SAC904 and SAC905: A Child's Garden (of Verses) - Robert Lewis Stevenson, 1964 (Box 37, Folder 630)
  - SAC906: (Treasury of) John Greenleaf Whittier, 1964 (Box 37, Folder 631)
  - SAC907 and SAC946: Walt Whitman I & II, 1966–1998 (Box 37, Folder 632)
  - SAC908 and SAC8025: Treasury of Lord Byron, 1964 (Box 37, Folder 633)
  - SAC911 and SAC912: (Treasury of)Andre Maurois, 1964 (Box 37, Folder 634)
  - SAC913 and SAC49-4: Treasury (of) Spanish Verse II, 1962 (Box 37, Folder 635)
  - SAC917-4: Sinews of Peace - Winston Churchill, 1966–1998 (Box 37, Folder 636)
  - SAC918 and SAC919: Chaucer and Beowulf, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 637)
  - SAC920: English Fairy Tales I, 1964 (Box 37, Folder 638)
  - SAC921, SAC922, SAC48-5, and SAC57-3: de Maupassant I and II, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 639)
  - SAC923: Disques Ades - Valery, Claudel, Perse, and Mauriac, undated (Box 37, Folder 640)
  - SAC925: English Fairy Tales II, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 641)
  - SAC926: Death of Patroclus, 1965–1989 (Box 37, Folder 642)
  - SAC927 and SAC802: Goldsmith/Gray/Collins, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 643)
  - SAC928: Echoes of Greece, 1965–1989 (Box 37, Folder 644)
  - SAC929: Jungle Book vol. I, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 645)
  - SAC931 and SAC932: Lettres de Mon Moulin - Georges Riquier, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 646)
  - SAC933: Jungle Book vol. II, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 647)
  - SAC934: Tennyson and Browning, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 648)
    NR contract [?].
  - SAC940, SAC941, SAC7028, and SAC7029: Hawthorne, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 649)
  - SAC942: Venus and Adonis, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 650)
  - SAC943: The Rape of Lucrece, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 651)
  - SAC944 and SAC945: Here Today vol. I and II, 1965–1989 (Box 37, Folder 652)
  - SAC947, SAC948, SAC949: Robert Speaight - Sonnets by Shakespeare, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 653)
  - SAC951: Jungle Book vol. III, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 654)
  - SAC952: Jungle Book vol. IV, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 655)
  - SAC954: The Song of Paul Bunyan and Tony Beaver, 1966–1989 (Box 37, Folder 656)
  - SAC955: Aesop's Fables, 1966–1989 (Box 37, Folder 657)
  - SAC956 and SAC957: Strangest Everything - Ciardi, 1966–1991 (Box 37, Folder 658)
  - SAC959, SAC8047 and SAC8048: She Stoops to Conquer, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 659)
    Non-royalty contract, full payment.
  - SAC961 and SAC8020: The Rape of the Lock, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 660)
  - SAC962: Pope, Alexander, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 661)
  - SAC966: The Inaugural Addresses of Washington, Lincoln, Jefferson, and T. Roosevelt, 1966–1989 (Box 37, Folder 662)
  - SAC967: Adventures of Tom Sawyer, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 663)
  - SAC968, SAC969, SAC970, SAC7142, SAC7143, and SAC7144: School for Scandal, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 664)
  - SAC971, SAC972, SAC8049, SAC8050: Sheridan's, The Rivals, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 665)
  - SAC973: Sonnets from the Portuguese, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 666)
  - SAC974 and SAC7128: Rubaiyat and Poems by Mattew Arnold, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 667)
  - SAC975, SAC976, and SAC977: Shakespearean Tales, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 668)
    Non-royalty contracts.
  - SAC978: Klein, Dr. (Arthur Luce), 1978–1996 (Box 37, Folder 669)
  - SAC982: Poker Flat and Roaring Camp, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 670)
  - SAC984: Poems of James Dickey - Weseyan University Press, 1967–1998 (Box 37, Folder 671)
  - SAC985: Provost, Jeanne - French Literature, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 672)
  - SAC989: Heroes, Gods, and Monsters of the Greek Myths, 1968–1998 (Box 37)
    - Music services company (Box 37, Folder 673)
    - Scholastic magazine (Box 38, Folder 674)
    - Julie Harris (Box 38, Folder 675)
  - SAC990: Poets for Peace, 1967–1989 (Box 38, Folder 676)
  - SAC993: Poetry of 16th Century, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 677)
  - SAC994 and SAC7122: Poetry of the Early 17th Century, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 678)
  - SAC995 and SAC996: Diary of Anais Nin - Mr. Gunther Stuhlmann, 1967–1998 (Box 38, Folder 679)
  - SAC998: Anthology of German Poetry, 1967–1998 (Box 38, Folder 680)
  - SAC999: W.H. Auden - Curtis Brown, 1968–1998 (Box 38, Folder 681)
  - Contract Letters, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 682)
  - SAC1005: Wiesel, Elie - George Borchant Inc., 1968–1998 (Box 38, Folder 683)
  - SAC1006: O Henry - Estate of Robert Ryan, 1968–1998 (Box 38, Folder 684)
  - SAC1007, SAC1008, and SAC1009: Twain, Mark and Hiram Sherman - Huck Finn, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 685)
  - SAC1010: The Rubayat of Omar Khayam, 1968–1998 (Box 38, Folder 686)
  - SAC1011, SAC1012, SAC7049, and SAC7050: Inaugural Addresses of Franklin Roosevelt, Harry Truman, Dwight Eisenhower, etc., 1968 (Box 38, Folder 687)
    Alexander Scourby. Non-royalty contract.
  - SAC1013 and SAC7003: Aesop's Fables, 1968 (Box 38, Folder 688)
  - SAC1019: Square That Number, 1967–1993 (Box 38, Folder 689)
  - SAC1021: World of Sholom Alechem, 1968–1993 (Box 38, Folder 690)
  - SAC1023 and PCC51: The Raven, The Bells, and Other Poems by Edgar Allan Poe - Hurd Hatfield, 1968–1998 (Box 38, Folder 691)
  - SAC1030 and SAC1031: Walk Together Children - Vinnie Burrows, 1968–1998 (Box 38, Folder 692)
  - SAC1037: Life in Shakespeare's London, 1968 (Box 38, Folder 693)
  - SAC1060, SAC1061, and SAC1062: Children's Anthology, Poems by William Blake, and Poems by D.H. Lawrence, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 694)
  - SAC1064, SAC7140, and PCC23: Selected Poems of Langston Hughes - Harold Ober Associates, 1969–1998 (Box 38, Folder 695)
  - SAC1068: Treasury of C. Day Lewis, 1969–1991 (Box 38, Folder 696)
  - SAC1069 and SAC7125: Letters of Romantic Poets, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 697)
  - SAC1070 and SAC848: Brer Rabbit - Prof. Ennis Rees, 1969–1998 (Box 38, Folder 698)
  - SAC1076: Old Tales of Japan, 1969–1998 (Box 39, Folder 699)
  - SAC1078: African Tales, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 700)
  - SAC1079: Folk and Fairy Tales from Italy, 1970, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 701)
  - SAC1086: Inaugural (Addresses of) Wilson, Hoover, and T. Roosevelt, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 702)
  - SAC1091 and SAC7173: Voices of Protest, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 703)
  - SAC1093: Stories of Isaac Babel, 1970–1971 (Box 39, Folder 704)
    Read by Joseph Wiseman. Non-royalty contract.
  - SAC1099: Promises to be Kept, 1971–1991 (Box 39, Folder 705)
  - SAC1100: Pleasures of Poetry, 1971–1992 (Box 39, Folder 706)
  - SAC1101 and SAC704: Wishes, Lies, and Dreams - International Creative, 1971–1998 (Box 39, Folder 707)
  - SAC1102: Someone Could Win a Polar Bear - Mrs. John Ciardi, 1971–1991 (Box 39, Folder 708)
  - SAC1103: Fairy Tales - Rapunzel, Princess Rosette, and The Little Good Mouse, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 709)
  - SAC1104, SAC1105, and SAC989: The Golden Touch and The Chimaera, 1971–1998 (Box 39, Folder 710)
  - SAC1106 and PCC70: Tales of the Hopi Tribe - Diane Wolkstein, 1971–1998 (Box 39, Folder 711)
  - SAC1106 -1107, and PCC70: California Tales - Diane Wolkstein, 1971–1998 (Box 39, Folder 712)
  - SAC1107: California Tales, 1971–1972 (Box 39, Folder 713)
  - SAC1108: "Indian Fairy Tales", 1972–1993 (Box 39, Folder 714)
    Never released. Contains contract for the production of stories from "Indian Fairy Tales" by Joseph Jacobs.
  - SAC1109: Heidi by Johanna Spyri, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 715)
  - SAC1110: The King of the Golden River by John Ruskin, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 716)
  - SAC1111: Black Beauty by Anne Sewell, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 717)
  - SAC1112: Hans Brinker of the Silver Skates by Mary Mapes Dodge, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 718)
  - SAC1113: Jack Tales - Billy Ed Wheller, 1971–1998 (Box 39, Folder 719)
  - SAC1114: Pablo Neruda (No Royalties) Ever Pia, 1972–1992 (Box 39, Folder 720)
  - SAC1115: What is Poetry?, 1972–1998 (Box 39, Folder 721)
  - SAC1117: London, Jack - Call of the Wild, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 722)
  - SAC1118: London, Jack - White Fang, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 723)
  - SAC1119: London, Jack - Seal Wolf, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 724)
  - SAC1120: Clockwork Orange, 1971–1998 (Box 39, Folder 725)
  - SAC1126: American Folk Songs and Ballads, 1974–1998 (Box 39, Folder 726)
  - SAC1132 and SAC1106: Eskimo Tales - Diane Wolkstein, 1974–1998 (Box 39, Folder 727)
  - SAC1132: Eskimo Tales - Diane Wolkstein, 1974–1977 (Box 39, Folder 728)
  - SAC1136: Spanish Songs and Ballads for Children, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 729)
  - SAC1137: Spanish Folk and Fairy Tales, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 730)
  - SAC1140: Jong, Erica - Fear of Flying, etc., 1976–1998 (Box 39, Folder 731)
  - SAC1141: The Entebbe Answer - Israel's Case Against International Terror, 1976–1977 (Box 40, Folder 732)
    Presentation by Ambassador Chaim Herzog - July 9 and 13, 1976.
  - SAC1142: Things that I Do in the Dark and other poems, 1978–1998 (Box 40, Folder 733)
    Read by June Jordan.
  - SAC1144: Stories of Grace Paley, 1978–1998 (Box 40, Folder 734)
  - SAC1151: Spoken Arts Treasury of Modern American Jewish Poets, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 735)
  - SAC1153: Singer, Isaac Bashevis, 1978–1998 (Box 40, Folder 736)
  - SAC1154: Poems of Kenneth Koch, 1979–1998 (Box 40, Folder 737)
  - SAC1155: Nuclear Folly, 1979–1994 (Box 40, Folder 738)
  - SAC1156: Thierfelder (III), W. (Dr. William), 1982 (Box 40, Folder 739)
    An Encounter with Carmen Conder. Non-royalty contract.
  - SAC1157: King, Christopher - 2 Soldiers, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 740)
  - SAC1159: The Sentinel, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 741)
  - SAC1160: Poems of Miller Williams, 1982–1998 (Box 40, Folder 742)
  - SAC1161: Poems of Paul Ramsey, 1983–1998 (Box 40, Folder 743)
  - SAC1162: Uses of Enchantment, 1985–1998 (Box 40, Folder 744)
  - SAC1164 and SAC1165: Rosa, 1990–1998 (Box 40, Folder 745)
    By Cynthia Ozick.
  - SAC1166 and SAC1167: Lessing, Doris - African Stories, 1990–1998 (Box 40, Folder 746)
  - SAC1168: Gordimer, Nadine - Short Stories, 1985–1998 (Box 40, Folder 747)
  - SAC1170: Poems of Sam Ragan, 1986–1998 (Box 40, Folder 748)
  - SAC1171: Poems of Howard Moss, 1986–1998 (Box 40, Folder 749)
  - SAC1173 and SAC1174: French Fairy Tales, 1985–1998 (Box 40, Folder 750)
  - SAC1175: The Man Who Mistook His Wife for a Hat, 1987–1989 (Box 40, Folder 751)
  - SAC1175 and SAC1176: The Man Who Mistook His Wife for a Hat and Awakenings, 1987–1998 (Box 40, Folder 752)
  - SAC1176: Sacks, Oliver - Awakenings, 1987 (Box 41, Folder 753)
  - SAC1177: West with the Night
    - 1 of 2, 1987–1998 (Box 41, Folder 754)
    - 2 of 2, 1989–1998 (Box 41, Folder 755)
  - SAC1178, SAC1179, and SAC1180: Contes de Maupassant, 1987–1998 (Box 41, Folder 756)
  - SAC1181 and SAC1182: Martin Luther King - James Baldwin, 1988–1998 (Box 41, Folder 757)
  - SAC1184: Moments of Insight, 1987–1998 (Box 41, Folder 758)
  - SAC1185: Poems by Rilke, 1989–1998 (Box 41, Folder 759)
  - SAC1198: Polish Songs for Children, 1989–1990 (Box 41, Folder 760)
  - SAC1201: Facing the Challenge of a New Age, 1991–1998 (Box 41, Folder 761)
  - SAC3002: The Black Experience, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 762)
  - SAC3003 and Mini Kit 25: Ives, Burl, 1971–1975 (Box 41, Folder 763)
  - SAC3004: Listener's Choice, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 764)
  - SAC3006: American Speeches, Ballads, and Documents, 1969 (Box 41, Folder 765)
  - SAC3009 (SAC1127, 28, 29, 30, and 35): Hecht, Paul, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 766)
  - SAC3041: Creating Character Voices, 1991–1998 (Box 41, Folder 767)
  - SAC3049: Lost and Found, 1989–1998 (Box 41, Folder 768)
  - SAC3050: I Am a Star, 1989–1998 (Box 41, Folder 769)
  - SAC4001: Talking with Mike, 1969–1998 (Box 41, Folder 770)
  - SAC4003: I Heard It with my Own Two Ears, 1969–1995 (Box 41, Folder 771)
  - SAC6500: World of Words, 1974–1998
    - vol. 1 (Box 41, Folder 772)
    - vol. 2 (Box 41, Folder 773)
  - SAC7021: Nature of Poetry, 1956, 1968-1998 (Box 42, Folder 774)
  - SAC7022 and SAC7023: Masque of the Red Death, 1967–1997 (Box 42, Folder 775)
  - SAC7043: Christmas Carol, 1956, 1966-1998 (Box 42, Folder 776)
  - SAC7048: Delight, 1956, 1968-1998 (Box 42, Folder 777)
  - SAC7136: Selected Poems of Stephen Spender, 1966–1998 (Box 42, Folder 778)
  - SAC7141: Anton Chekhov, 1962, 1978-1998 (Box 42, Folder 779)
  - SAC7145: Voice of the Turtle, 1956, 1968-1998 (Box 42, Folder 780)
  - SAC7146: The Who Came to Dinner, 1956, 1968-1998 (Box 42, Folder 781)
  - SAC7148: Krapp's Last Tape, 1960–1998 (Box 42, Folder 782)
  - SAC7149: Zoo Story, 1961–1998 (Box 42, Folder 783)
  - SAC7201 and SAC7202: Anne Frank, 1972–1998 (Box 42, Folder 784)
  - SAC7203 and SAC7204: Alice in Wonderland, 1973–1998 (Box 42, Folder 785)
    French.
  - SAC7500: Great Composer's Series, 1972–1998 (Box 42, Folder 786)
  - SAC7600: Your Own World, 1973–1998 (Box 42, Folder 787)
- Artist correspondence and related material, Series V
  Series is arranged by surname.
  - Anderson, Maxwell, 1956 (Box 43, Folder 788)
  - Atkinson, Brooks, 1956 (Box 43, Folder 789)
  - Baldwin, Faith: Informal Hour (I.H.), 1956 (Box 43, Folder 790)
  - Barzun, Jacques: America's Great Teachers, 1955–1956 (Box 43, Folder 791)
  - Baxter, Frank C.: America's Great Teachers, 1956 (Box 43, Folder 792)
  - Betjeman, John, 1956, undated (Box 43, Folder 793)
  - Brown, Kay: Kay Brown, Audrey Wood, and B. Brenner, 1956 (Box 43, Folder 794)
    MCA.
  - Bryson, Lyman: Great Teachers Series, 1956 (Box 43, Folder 795)
  - Buck, Pearl: Informal Hour (I.H.), 1956 (Box 43, Folder 796)
  - Caldwell, Erskine: James O. Brown, 1956 (Box 43, Folder 797)
  - Campell, Oscar James: America's Great Teachers, 1956 (Box 43, Folder 798)
  - Cerf, Bennett A.: Inf. Informal Hour, 1956 (Box 43, Folder 799)
  - Colum, Padraic, 1956 (Box 43, Folder 800)
    Includes photograph.
  - Copland, Aaron, 1956 (Box 43, Folder 801)
  - Cowley, Malcolm, 1956 (Box 43, Folder 802)
  - de Ceballos: Celtic Songs, 1955–1956 (Box 43, Folder 803)
  - Deutsch, Babette: Informal Hour (I.H.), 1956 (Box 43, Folder 804)
  - Dobie, J. Frank: Informal Hour (I.H.), 1956 (Box 43, Folder 805)
  - Dos Passos, John, 1956 (Box 43, Folder 806)
  - Fadiman, Clifton, 1956 (Box 43, Folder 807)
  - French Verse Correspondence, 1955–1956 (Box 43, Folder 808)
  - Gassner, John: Teacher, 1956 (Box 43, Folder 809)
  - Gottschalk, Louis: America's Great Teachers, 1956 (Box 43, Folder 810)
  - Green, Paul: Great Playwright Series, 1956 (Box 43, Folder 811)
  - Hart, Moss: Great Playwright Series, 1956 (Box 43, Folder 812)
  - Hellman, Lillian: Great Playwright Series, 1956 (Box 43, Folder 813)
  - Hutchins, Robert M.: America's Great Teachers, 1956 (Box 43, Folder 814)
  - Jones, Howard Mumford: America's Great Teachers, 1956 (Box 43, Folder 815)
  - Lehman, B.H.: America's Great Teachers, 1956 (Box 43, Folder 816)
  - Lunt and Fontanne: Great Artists Series, 1956 (Box 43, Folder 817)
  - McKenna, Siobhan: "Piccoli" - Great Artists Series, 1956 (Box 43, Folder 818)
    Simon and Shuster, Inc.
  - MacNeill, Robert, 1988 (Box 43, Folder 819)
  - Masefield, John: An Informal Hour with …, 1956 (Box 43, Folder 820)
  - Miscellaneous: An Informal Hour with …, 1956 (Box 43, Folder 821)
    Writers' series.
  - Miscellaneous: Distinguished Teachers Series, 1956 (Box 43, Folder 822)
  - Morris, Richard B.: Great Teachers Series, 1956 (Box 43, Folder 823)
  - O'Melia, Davis: French Verse, 1956 (Box 43, Folder 824)
    Translation.
  - Parker, Dorothy: An Informal Hour with …, 1956 (Box 43, Folder 825)
  - Pettingell, Frank, 1956 (Box 43, Folder 826)
  - Priestley, J.B. (writer), 1956 (Box 43, Folder 827)
  - Quayle, Anthony: Great Artists Series, 1956 (Box 43, Folder 828)
  - Radio Eireann: Robert Farren, 1956 (Box 43, Folder 829)
  - Reik, Theodore, 1958, undated (Box 43, Folder 830)
  - Rice, Elmer: Great Playwrights Series, 1956 (Box 43, Folder 831)
  - Robinson, Edward G.: Great Artists Series, 1956 (Box 44, Folder 832)
  - Rogers, Paul: Great Artists Series, 1956 (Box 44, Folder 833)
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor: Informal Hour (I.H.), 1956 (Box 44, Folder 834)
  - Ryder, Frank G: German Verse, 1956 (Box 44, Folder 835)
  - Schnitzler, Henry, 1956, undated (Box 44, Folder 836)
  - Schuman, Frederick L.: America's Great Teachers, 1956 (Box 44, Folder 837)
  - Shapiro, Dr. Sumner, 1987–1989 (Box 44, Folder 838)
  - Slosson, Preston: America's Great Teachers, 1955–1956 (Box 44, Folder 839)
  - Smith, Lillian, 1956 (Box 44, Folder 840)
  - Smith, T.V.: America's Great Teachers, 1956 (Box 44, Folder 841)
  - Splendid Outcast [The]: Markham, 1987–1989 (Box 44, Folder 842)
    Markham, read by Frances Sternhagen and West with the Night: Markham, read by Julie Harris.
  - Teller, Edward: America's Great Teachers, 1956 (Box 44, Folder 843)
  - Trilling, Lionel: America's Great Teachers, 1956 (Box 44, Folder 844)
  - Van Druten, John and Monica McCall: Playwrights, 1956 (Box 44, Folder 845)
  - Vilar, Jean: French Verse, 1956 (Box 44, Folder 846)
  - Williams, Dr. Miller, 1987–1989 (Box 44, Folder 847)
- Records on special projects, Series VI
  Series is arranged by PCC then JP numbers, with unnumbered material at the end of the series.
  - PCC 43-4: Kaplan, Hyman, 1966–1998 (Box 44, Folder 848)
  - PCC44-4X: Strange Fruit, 1966–1998 (Box 44, Folder 849)
  - PCC44-5X: Our Faces, Our Words, 1965–1998 (Box 44, Folder 850)
  - PCC44-6: The Loves of Charles II, 1961–1998 (Box 44, Folder 851)
  - PCC74: Wanderer of the Wasteland, 1986–1998 (Box 44, Folder 852)
    Zane Grey, Inc.
  - PCC75 and PCC74: The Vanishing American, 1986–1998 (Box 44, Folder 853)
  - PCC78V and PCC78: Wordstruck - Viking, 1989–1998 (Box 44, Folder 854)
    Needy Productions.
  - PCC79-7 and PCC79: The Splendid Outcast, 1989–1998 (Box 44, Folder 855)
  - JP-4: 63 Dream Palace - James Purdy, 1969–1989 (Box 44, Folder 856)
    Contract.
  - JP-4E: Color of Darkness and Eventide - James Purdy, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 857)
  - JP-4E: Eventide - James Purdy, 1969–1987 (Box 44, Folder 858)
  - American Wake, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 859)
    Contract, not released.